module.exports = {
	config: {
		name: "ترتيب", // Name of command, it must be unique to identify with other commands
		version: "1.0", // Version of command
		author: "Eslam", // Author of command
		countDown: 5, // Time to wait before executing command again (seconds)
		role: 0, // Role of user to use this command (0: normal user, 1: admin box chat, 2: owner bot)
		shortDescription: {
			vi: "đây là mô tả ngắn của lệnh",
			en: "this is short description of command"
		}, // Short description of command
		longDescription: {
			vi: "đây là mô tả dài của lệnh",
			en: "لعبة"
		}, // Long description of command
		category: "categoryName", // Category of command
		guide: {
			vi: "đây là hướng dẫn sử dụng của lệnh",
			en: "this is guide of command"
		} // Guide of command
	},

	langs: {
		vi: {
			hello: "xin chào",
			helloWithName: "xin chào, id facebook của bạn là %1"
		}, // Vietnamese language
		en: {
			hello: "hello world",
			helloWithName: "hello, your facebook id is %1"
		} // English language
	},

	// onStart is a function that will be executed when the command is executed
	onStart: async function ({ api, args, message, event, threadsData, usersData, dashBoardData, globalData, threadModel, userModel, dashBoardModel, globalModel, role, commandName, getLang }) {
		// YOUR CODE HERE
    
              let questions = [
             {
                  question: "ر م ص",
                  answer: "مصر"
                },
                {
                  question: "ج ا ز ل ا ئ ر",
                  answer: "الجزائر"
                },
                {
                  question: "ش ط م",
                  answer: "مشط"
                },
                {
                  question: "ة م ع ش",
                  answer: "شمعة"
                },
                {
                  question: "ب س ا ح ",
                  answer: "سحاب"
                }, {
                  question: "ر ق م",
                  answer: "قمر"
                }, {
                  question: " ل م ك",
                  answer: "ملك"
                }, {
                  question: " ا ا ل ر ن ر ج",
                  answer: "الجنرار"
                }, {
                  question: "ر ز ي و ا ل",
                  answer: "الوزير"
                }, {
                  question: "ا و ج ل ل",
                  answer: "الجول"
                }, {
                  question: "ب ر ا غ ئ",
                  answer: "غرائب"
                }, {
                  question: "ا م ل ك",
                  answer: "كلام"
                }, {
                  question: "ب ع ئ ج ا ",
                  answer: "عجائب"
                }, {
                  question: "ق ر ز ا ة ",
                  answer: "قزارة"
                }, {
                  question: "ع ج ة م",
                  answer: "جمعة"
                }, {
                  question: "ج و ا م ل ن",
                  answer: "النجوم"
                }, {
                  question: "ز م ن ل ا",
                  answer: "الزمن"
                }, {
                  question: "د ص ا ا ل ع",
                  answer: "الصداع"
                }, {
                  question: "ح ة ي ا ا ل",
                  answer: "الحياة"
                }, {
                  question: "ن ل ص ا ة ي ح",
                  answer: "النصيحة"
                }, {
                  question: "ا س ل ن ا ن ا ",
                  answer: "الإنسان"
                }, {
                  question: "ث ن ا ل ع ب ا ",
                  answer: "الثعبان"
                }, {
                  question: "ا ا ل ر ن",
                  answer: "النار"
                }, {
                  question: "ص ا ت ل م",
                  answer: "الصمت"
                }, {
                  question: "ل س ا ة ع ",
                  answer: "الساعة"
                },   
              ];
              let randomIndex = Math.floor(Math.random() * questions.length);
              let randomQuestion = questions[randomIndex].question;
              let answer = questions[randomIndex].answer;
              api.sendMessage(randomQuestion, event.threadID, (err, messageInfo)=>{
                let stopListening = api.listenMqtt((err, event) => {
                if (err) return console.error(err);

                switch (event.type) {
                  case "message":
                    if(event.threadID === messageInfo.threadID){
                      if (event.body === answer) {               api.sendMessage("جميل انت سريع", event.threadID, event.messageID);
                      return stopListening();
                    } else if (event.body === 'ترتيب') {
                      return stopListening();
                    }
                    api.markAsRead(event.threadID, (err) => {
                      if (err) console.log(err);
                    });
                    }

                    break;
                }
              });
              });

	}
};